It's my life, it's your life, fighting
for tomorrow, go get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life, run
like the wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong, believe
you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going on the stairs.
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
Know what you're making my dream. Time to.
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is.
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
The greater no day I know you.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wild.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you.
Only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
But it won't you more walk.
It's what you really want.
I want more, anyone more.
Come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high.
I know you're strong.
Believe you cannot achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, rolling.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your wife that I
want, but you're where it was.
I want more, and you want more.
Come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your life.
Shine like a star to be good, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Tells that you gotta keep your best.
Let's keep on going, I'm not dead.
You make my day every day.
I'm so glad you're safe. Congenal!
Oh, Kin'emon.
At long last, my heart dances.
My apologies.
It seems I was troublesome to find.
I encountered one strange
occurrence after another,
so I thought it might be wise to hide
in the wall until danger had passed.
However, it seems I fell asleep.
You're truly a remarkable friend.
I'm grateful that you came back for me.
I kept you waiting.
Forgive me.
Cap, cap, cap.
There's no cause for regret.
I would gladly wait for my
friend as long as it took.
I trust you.
Thanks to my sorcery, I
was able to conceal myself.
I could produce sustenance as well.
Where are my married?
Perhaps you have not
been as fortunate as I.
Want some lettuce?
No, I'm fine.
Your food never agrees with my stomach.
Ha! Ha! Ha!
I trust that Momonosuke
is in good health as well.
Indeed he is, thanks to you. Good news.
In that case, I hope that
we can be reunited soon.
Likewise.
I'm sure Momonosuke will be
eager to see you as well.
A great many things have happened
since the two of us parted ways.
Far too many to explain.
Doing so we'll have to wait until another
time we must make haste very well,
then let us depart
Does that mean they know a way out?
Painting what's that gonna do?
Now come forth
Spring Sparrow!
This is weird!
He must have devil-proof powers!
It's moving on its own!
The picture of a bird just came to life!
He's a crappy artist, though.
Looks awful.
That's an amazing power, but
he can't draw birds at all.
Poor thing can barely fly.
No, Kin'emon.
Away we go.
Hold on, you two.
The people here are King Riku's soldiers
and citizens who were once toys.
We need to know if King
Rick is alive, please.
We're so lost right now.
Our families are waiting for us up in this
city—is there any way you can take us?
We're trapped.
There's
fire.
Why don't you try aiming at us too!
too
Guillotine high-heeled!
The long-legged guy got beat! Enough!
Eyes forward, Straw Hat!
We have one objective, and that's
making it to Doflamingo's palace!
The moment that I heard him make
that announcement to everyone,
I realized the bitter truth.
Your objective is to assassinate me.
it's kill or be killed every person in
the kingdom is now a bounty hunter and
the only way for you to survive it's
free to take the life of another person
the so-called game of his
is nothing but a death trap
As soon as Doflamingo's weapon
trafficking was revealed,
along with the truth of the toys,
I suspect that every person in this
kingdom was given a death sentence.
Doflamingo won't let any
information escape from Dressrosa.
That's the real reason why he locked
the kingdom inside this birdcage.
Now do you realize what the situation is?
He's created a solitary island cut
off from the rest of the world.
The citizens,
who are waiting for a miracle or trying
to play the game, will all be killed.
The only way to escape the
island and save its people from
this massacre is to get rid of
Doflamingo before it's too late.
The kingdom has been
thrown into absolute chaos.
But even though the situation
is spiraling out of control,
strangely, Doflamingo seems
to be enjoying himself.
He's the most cunning
adversary I've ever met.
I'm certain of that.
And yet, despite his strength and
obvious advantages in this situation,
Doflamingo still made one key error.
He held a tournament at the Coliseum
and invited an army of powerful and,
more importantly,
strong-willed fighters into his kingdom.
There's no way we'll submit to him.
Especially me.
I will defeat Doflamingo
with my own hands!
Stop saying that!
I already called Gibbs on
Mingo like a million times!
This one's personal.
Doflamingo's mine.
While your passion is
admirable, this is my fight.
That's cheating!
You said you wanted one of the
executives and nobody complained!
As a personal matter, yes.
But it's my duty to take back this
kingdom in the name of King Rick.
For ten years, I have waited
to put an end to this tragedy.
Well, my grudge is from 13 years ago.
How about that?
Then mine is from 30 years ago!
Dirty liar! You're not 30!
You're not even as old as I am!
Get off my horse!
You get off my horse!
That doesn't make sense!
That's what you get for inviting me!
We're at the end of the road!
I can see it!
That's the third level!
Okay, ignore that and
keep running like this!
Straight up to the palace!
Go, horse!
There's something the matter, Foggy.
Holy, what the heck are those things?
Just saying, if this is all you've got,
you never had a chance against my captain.
Little... twat!
Ah, damn it!
Too slow.
Why are you here and why are you flying?
Zoro.
Well, do I get to see Mr. Zoro fight?
I'm stuck in the sky.
I gotta get down there
and get an autograph.
Oh no, that's Pika.
Rebecca.
Who's that?
He's the top executive from the family.
with the same rank as Treble and Diamante.
Zoro, keep the enemy right
there. Huh? We're going up.
We have to pass over this stone figure.
Huh?
That should be easy enough.
I'm just trying to figure
out how you're flying.
Looks like our enemy ran away.
Crap, he tricked us!
You won't get to the palace!
He's back inside.
Here he comes.
This guy's aiming straight for us.
Use your barrier.
I can't, jeez.
I gotta use my hands for that.
Being fast.
We gotta do something.
Cause any second now
we're gonna get smashed.
Just never reach.
Three sword style.
1 ,080-caliber phoenix!
I think I get how your power works.
There's something I forgot to tell you.
You've underestimated the Straw Hats.
Lupi and Usopp aren't the only
ones you need to worry about.
See this face?
You're looking at the
man who's going to be
the greatest swordsman
in the world someday.
Mr. Sorrow!
I would be thrilled to help.
One moment, please.
Brilliant.
Thank you, samurai.
We can finally get out of here.
Take turns climbing up.
The ladders are not particularly sturdy.
We could climb better if
the lines were straight.
Well, that's just hurtful.
How rude.
The little people are causing a riot!
We need backup!
We're screwed.
They're just too fast to hit.
Just keep firing. You'll get one.
You guys are bad and your aim is bad, too.
You'll never beat us
Wait, you can't aren't you worried
about Princess Mon Cherie? Huh?
We have to take care of her
because she's so sick if you leave
the factory with her then how
is she ever gonna get better?
I didn't even consider that He's
tricking us You can't listen, Chou
Come on Let's put this business
behind us And get back to work, okay
I put in earplugs So I can't
hear your nasty lies anymore
Santana, swing!
Call the young master. Hurry.
Okay. Hey!
You guys better not!
Tantata tail!
Ford and Hammer!
Okay, let's release
their transponder snails.
If we do that, they won't be
able to call for backup anymore.
Are you paying attention? Huh?
Your earplugs!
I'm pleased to know her illness was alive,
But to think that she's been alone
all this time in the factory.
How sad she must be.
Princess, your loyal Mouji understand.
I can practically see
the tears on your cheeks.
Why, I can practically hear
you calling out my name.
Mouji, wait.
That's the isolation ward.
Moucherie must be in there.
Don't worry, I'll save you.
Hold on, you can't do it.
Why would you say that?
Look at that sign up on the door.
It says keep out!
That means we can't go in there!
Oh no!
What a tragedy!
Why didn't anyone tell me until now?
It's far too late for me to slow down!
He crashed right through that door like
the keep out sign wasn't even there!
I'm so disappointed in you!
Your blatant disregard for
the rules makes us look bad!
I'm sorry...
I can't find her!
Is everybody ready?
Let's go, Lurch!
Faster!
Whoa!
Oh!
Oh, you're so relentless, senor.
Almost there.
Huh?
Franky Ear.
Unlike the rest of his body, his
ears have no mechanical advantage.
However, his hearing is naturally
quite good, so he gets along just fine.
Listen,
Something's been bugging me, hmm.
It's not the kind of thing you'd
care about, I guess, but uh,
earlier I saw this sweet old granny having
a tough time on that street over there,
and it darn near broke my heart.
Is that so?
You sure hate to see that?
Not so fast, little shrimps.
You think I'm gonna let you out better?
Remember who's in charge of this place.
That's the manager.
We're in big trouble now.
Pathetic!
You twerps have been
here all this time and
you just now realized
you're nothing but slaves?
I'll put you back to work!
Break time is over!
Don't be layabout!
Come here!
If we don't come up with
something quick, we're finished!
Open the door!
That's our only hope!
Nice work, now let's party!
It's a robot!
A big strong robot game to save us!
Thank you, sir!
So cool!
The robots are awesome!
Is everybody okay? Yeah!
We made it!
We're breaking all you guys out of here!
I'm so happy.
Good for you. Thank you, Mr. Robot.
He has a name and he's not a robot.
He's a big person, the great
hero known as Frawland.
What kind of person is
this princess of yours?
Hmm, where does that...
Don't ignore me!
We never settle things between
us, you bunch of little dolts!
The factory is my life!
I'm the manager, you punks!
When they call me to the scene,
you know you're in for it!
You're Cyborg Franky from the
Straw Hat Pirates, aren't you?
I thought you only had a one-star bounty!
How did you make it this far
with a target on your head?
Senor Pink should have
stopped you. Yeah? You think?
Anyway, this is my factory.
I won't let you have the run of the place.
You step up to this lady, you die!
Frolin, be careful. She's strong.
Frolin gave the man Julie a great big hug!
Hey, what's the big idea here?
You're being weird. Let go!
Valen just keeps hugging her.
Bastard fooled me.
That dirty, lying cyborg.
I was all worried about that
granny, but she isn't even real.
Well, at least I don't have to worry now.
Oh, so are Niles!
Hey, Senor Pink.
I'm ready to go again anytime.
Bring it on, bro.
This is not appropriate behavior for a
workplace environment, okay? You know,
that big baby has been rattling my head
with suplexes one after another all day.
Huh?
What's the deal?
Maybe he thought my head was a jackhammer
and he was trying to dig himself a hole.
You've really lost it, haven't you?
I'm taking you out.
Cat Ear Punch!
The Ranky Southland Suplex!
Uh-oh, she's really mad, uh-oh.
That hurts, you bastard!
Didn't your mama ever tell you
that's no way to treat a lady?
You think you can get away with that?
What?
In my factory?
I'm the manager here!
That means nobody is above me!
I don't care how nice your hugs are.
Once she gets this mad,
there's no stopping her.
Run away, Froland!
I'm gonna cut you into tiny pieces,
then suck them up with my vacuum,
then dump them out and stomp on them!
then suck them up all over again!
So start crying, not that
it'll do you any good!
Froland gave the manager a great big kiss!
My, how daring!
He stole a kiss from these sweet lips!
You gonna lay there and drown, or what?
Hold on, Franky!
What was that?
I didn't know you felt that way about me!
Everything's moving so fast!
If that's how you feel about a girl,
then you should ask her out first, dummy!
I never knew she had a girly side.
This is a shock.
It ain't his fault, Miss Manager.
That's how it goes. Huh?
Love's got nothing to do with it.
Even though he kissed me?
That's right, because you caught him
during a sacred fight between two men.
He had to seal those lips somehow, and
a smooch is the easiest way to do it.
One little kiss ain't no thing, sister.
This is a battlefield, not
some daycare playground.
You think I'm looking for
romance in a time like this?
You said it.
Who needs baby love?
We're living in a man's world.
They're so hard-boiled!
Franky! Senor!
You're the perfect hard-boiled duo!
I'm not gonna let you
wreck this factory, robot.
Then prove it with your
fists, if you're a man!
I'm almost scared.
It's gonna get so manly!
Diaper bombs!
Nipple Light Special!
Would you stop turning
into rocks and fight me?
I almost had them and now
Rebecca's getting away!
Yeah, thanks, pal.
Couldn't have done it without you.
You and your friends are
gonna die in this cage!
There could be enemies
waiting on the second level.
Let's be careful where we jump off.
Hello, Leo here.
This is Mouji.
Oh, good, you're free.
I guess that means
everyone else is too then?
Indeed we are, but I have some awful news.
Whoa, what is it, Mouji?
The princess, Princess Moucherie.
It seems she isn't at the factory.
The poor little dear, she must
be locked up somewhere awful,
calling my name again and again!
What should we do?
March to the old king's plateau!
Surround King Rick and God Usopp!
Nothing to be scared of just yet.
We're in a good spot.
Who knows if they can
even climb up this high.
Find God Usopp and string him up!
I have good news!
All the Tontaras have been set free!
Oh? At the factory? Yes.
But, they said they can't
find Princess Mon Cherie.
She's not there?
None of that matters right now!
Everyone in the whole
kingdom is trying to kill us!
We need to run away!
If everyone in the whole kingdom is after
us, then there's nowhere safe to go.
It's fine.
Now they all know the truth
about what happened in the past.
The people won't harm father.
I'm certain of that.
What about me? Viola. Yes? Hello?
If they're hiding Princess Monchery, she
must be somewhere in the royal palace.
She must be well hidden.
Search every nook and cranny.
The flamingo wouldn't be
foolish enough to kill Monchery.
Her ability is far too
valuable for him to lose.
Frankly, we could use that
ability ourselves at the moment.
Take it.
Time to eat.
I just want to go back to Green Bed.
Won't anybody come save me?
Leo!